Kidnapped: Elizabeth Smart is a documentary, crime
film directed by Benedict Sanderson.
Elizabeth Smart's harrowing abduction at 14 from her family's Utah home unfolds
through her own words and never-before-seen material in this documentary.
Self, played by Elizabeth Smart.
Detective, played by Steevan Glover.
Brian David Mitchell, played by John Stableforth.
Self (archive footage), played by Brian David Mitchell.
Self (archive footage), played by Wanda Barzee.
Self (archive footage), played by Soledad O'Brien.
Amber Marshall (born June 2, 1988) is a Canadian
actress, singer, and equestrian.
She has appeared in several television films and series, most notably as
Amy Fleming in the long-running CBC/Up TV series Heartland.
For her performance in the series, Marshall won the inaugural Canada's
Screen Star Award at the 1st Canadian Screen Awards.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, utah, psychology, trauma, victim.